In the last question involving this data structure,
涉及这个资料结构的最后一个问题
we want to create a dictionary that contains the hexamesters as the keys
我们想要建立一个字典 包含学期 (hexamesters) 作为 key
and the values as a list of each course a given person is involved with.
value 是个列表 与某个人参与 (involved) 的课程列表
So let's look at Dave.
现在 我们看看 Dave
For April 2012 he's involved in 2 courses:
在 2012 年 4 月 他参与了两个课程
cs101, his intro course, and cs387, the Applied Cryptography course.
cs101 计算机科学简介课程 和 cs387 应用加密技术课程
And the dictionary continues on, but the structure stays the same,
字典继续下去 但结构保持不变
where the key is the hexamester and the value is a list of courses
key 是学期 (hexamester)  而 value 是那个人所参与
for which that person is involved.
的课程列表
So 1 question you may be asking yourself, what does it mean to be involved?
所以你可能会问自己一个问题 “参与” (involved) 是什么意思？
And if we go back to our data structure, what we're going to do
如果回到我们的资料结构 我们要做的是
is look at the name value pairs associated with the course.
看看与课程相关的 'name/value' 配对
So if we're looking for Steve, Steve is associated with his class, cs253,
所以如果我们寻找 Steve Steve 与 cs253
the Web Engineering - Building a Blog.
网站开发课程相关
And so that's what we're going to do.
这就是我们要做的事
We're going to go through each course, looking at the value in the name value pairs,
我们要走遍每个课程 去看 'name/value' 配对中的 value
and if the value is what we're looking for,
如果 value 是我们正在寻找的值
then we're going to add that course to our dictionary
那么我们就把这个课程加入字典
associated with the key of that hexamester.
这个字典与学期 (hexamester) 的 key 相关
It sounds a little convoluted, and the answer is a little long,
这听起来有点令人难以理解 而答案也有点长
but it's really a simple idea.
但它真的只是一个简单的想法
The first thing I'm doing is creating the output dictionary.
我要做的第一件事是建立 output 字典
We're going to go through each hexamester.
我们要走遍每个学期 (hexamester)
We're going to go through each course in each hexamester.
我们要走遍每学期的每一门课
We're going to go through each key in the name value pairs.
我们要走遍 'name/value' 的每个 key
If the value associated with all this is the person we're looking for,
如果与这些相关的 value 是我们要寻找的人
then we're going to update our output dictionary.
那么我们要更新我们的 output 字典
If we've already added this hexamester as a key to the output dictionary,
如果这个学期已经是 output 字典的 key
then we're just going to append this course at the end of the list
我们只要将课程加到与学期相关的
associated with that hexamester.
列表末尾
Otherwise we're going to create a new list for which the course is the sole value,
否则 我们要建立新的列表 这门课程是它唯一的值
and once we're done with all these for loops, we're going to return our output dictionary.
一旦我们完成了 for loop 我们传回 output 字典